(Sheldon:)into a one-act play.
(Penny:)And you think it's better
than Tennessee Williams?
(Sheldon:)Why don't we leave that for
future generations to decide?
Where No Sheldon
Has Gone Before.
(Sheldon:)It's the story of a young boy
who is transported
(Sheldon:)from the ignorant backwoods
of East Texas
(Sheldon:)to the 23rd Century,
(Sheldon:)where his genius is not only
appreciated, but celebrated.
(Sheldon:)KMN...
(Sheldon:)Now, in this
pivotal scene,
(Sheldon:)Sheldon's mother, played by you,
argues with an emissary
(Sheldon:)of the United Federation
of Planets, Mr. Spock,
(Sheldon:)the role I will bring to life.
(Penny:)Okay, that's fine,
but let's try
(Penny:)and get you out
of your comfort zone.
(Sheldon:)Why would we want to do that?
It's called "the comfort zone"
for a reason.
(Penny:)Okay, the whole point of this is
to loosen you up a little,
(Penny:)so I'm thinking you'll play
the role of your mother,
(Penny:)and I will bring life
to Mr. Spock.